{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "English for Academic & Professional Purposes",
    "Term": "First Quarter",
    "Title": "Writing Process and Outlining",
    "LastModified": "16 August 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "What is a form of communication that is shaped by factors?",
      "answer": "Writing",
      "choices": [
        "Outlining",
        "Writing",
        "Thesis Statement",
        "Topic Sentence"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Writing Process"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the overall idea or arguments of your work?",
      "answer": "Thesis statement",
      "choices": [
        "Topic Sentence",
        "Thesis statement",
        "Outline",
        "Writing"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Key Writing Components"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a general statement that presents essential points that leads the reader to the right direction?",
      "answer": "Thesis statement",
      "choices": [
        "Topic Sentence",
        "Thesis statement",
        "Outline",
        "Writing"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Key Writing Components"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is included as a sentence or as part of the text?",
      "answer": "Explicit Thesis Statement",
      "choices": [
        "Implicit Thesis Statement",
        "Explicit Thesis Statement",
        "Topic Sentence",
        "Traditional Outline"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Thesis Statements"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is it when the primary point of the reading is conveyed indirectly, in multiple locations throughout the work?",
      "answer": "Implicit Thesis Statement",
      "choices": [
        "Explicit Thesis Statement",
        "Implicit Thesis Statement",
        "Topic Sentence",
        "Standard Outline"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Thesis Statements"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a tool we use in the writing process to help organize our ideas, visualize our paper's potential structure?",
      "answer": "Outlining",
      "choices": [
        "Outlining",
        "Clustering",
        "Brainstorming",
        "Free Writing"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Pre-writing Stage"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a step to produce ideas for writing that groups the ideas according to their relevance?",
      "answer": "Outlining",
      "choices": [
        "Clustering",
        "Outlining",
        "Brainstorming",
        "Free Writing"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Pre-writing Stage"
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of outline uses roman numerals, letters and numbers?",
      "answer": "Traditional Outline",
      "choices": [
        "Standard Outline",
        "Traditional Outline",
        "Parallelism",
        "Subordination"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Kinds of Outline"
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of outline uses numbers?",
      "answer": "Standard Outline",
      "choices": [
        "Standard Outline",
        "Traditional Outline",
        "Coordination",
        "Division"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Kinds of Outline"
    },
    {
      "question": "What principle of outlining is it when entries should observe the same language structure?",
      "answer": "Parallelism",
      "choices": [
        "Coordination",
        "Subordination",
        "Parallelism",
        "Division"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Principles of Outlining"
    },
    {
      "question": "What principle of outlining is it when entries should observe level of importance?",
      "answer": "Coordination",
      "choices": [
        "Coordination",
        "Subordination",
        "Parallelism",
        "Division"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Principles of Outlining"
    },
    {
      "question": "What principle of outlining is it when entries should observe differences of importance?",
      "answer": "Subordination",
      "choices": [
        "Coordination",
        "Subordination",
        "Parallelism",
        "Division"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Principles of Outlining"
    },
    {
      "question": "What principle of outlining is it when entries should at least be two to be sure that supporting points of a major idea are adequate?",
      "answer": "Division",
      "choices": [
        "Coordination",
        "Subordination",
        "Parallelism",
        "Division"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Principles of Outlining"
    }
  ]
}